Exercise 6-8, hold your tongue. You and I are going to read with our tongues firmly
held at the roofs of our mouths. If you want, hold a clean dime there with the
tongue's tip. The dime will let you know when you've dropped your tongue because it
will fall out. Do not use candy. It will hold itself there since wet candy is
sticky. If you prefer, you can read with your tongue between your teeth instead of
the standard behind the teeth position and use a small mirror. Remember that with
this technique, you can actually see your tongue disappear. L sounds drop off. It's
going to sound ridiculous, of course, and nobody would ever intentionally sound like
this, but no one will hear you practice. You don't want to sound like this. Force
your tongue to make all the various vowels in spite of its position. Let's go. Viva
Lofroa!